to try and get some clout and you know
what let's say I did get broken y'all
will be the first ones to be like see
y'all be doing too much no big up to all
my strong black women who are supporting
other strong black women and every other
person supporting us we love you the
rest of y'all can suck
up is this y'all
leader is this y'all leader now Amanda
listen I'm not laughing at you let me
stop lying yes I am listen okay listen
put the video back up put the video back
up honest had
okay I got my hand don't worry about my
nails I could not do my nails during
spring break them children are bad
listen Okay so she got 2.2 million
followers she is angry over an
opinion this is an opinion piece